ufonts.com 2015-06-07

# µfonts Privacy Statement

ufonts.com have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

ufonts only gathers basic non-specific personal information, these are.  
\- Name (Can be a nickname if you prefer),  
\- Country (To make downloads faster for you) and   
\- Email addresses (see below).  
These details also help personalise your experience of ufonts.com 

ufonts.com does not disclose any of your details including email addresses to third parties. Your email address is used for administrative purposes only, such as password changes. You do not _have_ to provide an email address, however it is recommended, without one there is no way to recover your account if you forget your password!

None of the software on ufonts.com contains adware, spyware, trojans, or other malicious code.

ufonts.com, sparingly uses Pop-up advertisments to fund the operating and other running costs of the website.

Whenever a user views a page located on this website, certain information is logged. This information includes the user's IP address, browser, and where the user came from. This is standard information collected by most Web servers.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Also please note when posting to an online forum or submitting data through any of the scripts located on this site, such as image validation sequences, your IP address may be stored along with this information. 

"Cookies" are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow the web site to remember important information that will make your use of the site more convenient. Like most web sites, ufonts.com uses cookies to operate our security systems and specific content to download files. We associate your account information with a cookie file in these instances. 

Use the options in your web browser if you do not wish to receive a cookie or if you wish to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Click on the "Help" section of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you disable all cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all the features of this web site.

ufonts.com makes use of chat rooms, and message boards, Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

This site contains content and advertisements delivered via third parties. ufonts.com is not responsible for the privacy practices and/or the content of such Web sites. When visiting such sites, we urge you to be an informed surfer and use caution when providing any personal data. 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These measures include secure servers, encrypted passwords, and other security measures to guarantee the privacy of our members. 

You may contact ufonts.com here
